User Interface, experience and Brand Designer



Tel: (+47) 455 07 088 predrage@pm.me

Predrag has over 18 years of work experience in design and web development. Open and creative approach helps him design inclusive and accessible product and service experience that fits seamlessly into people's lives. App interface design and solution development beside webdesign are his main areas of expertise and professional interest.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Interactive Designer, Sixty, Bergen — 2018 — now

User Experience and Interface design for sport applications and new generation of interactive TV graphics. Developing technologies that enable user interactivity within digital broadcast. Had an opportunity to work with major global brands from US to Asia (more under references page 2).

Designer, FrontEnd Developer, Intutor Group, Bergen — 2012–2018

Developed and worked on some of the biggest systems in Norway;
Developing systems from scratch, system for traffic schools and students;
Real-estate documentation processing, distributing and archiving;
Kindergarten system for administration and communication; Innovating in field of IoT APP with sensor technologies; Providing web services to many companies and organizations.

Designer, Consultant, Shanghai, China — 2011, 2012

"Apollo BC", ANS-architects and Event Marketing Agency. Worked with wine distributers on promotions of different wine regions for the Chinese market.

Vino & Fino Magazine — 2012

Designer, Developer, Human Vision web studio, Serbia — 2007-2011

Designer and Developer, co-founder with several developers and marketers focused on innovation in e-commerce and social networking.

Co-founder, Designer for Magazine "Gurman Press" — 2002–2006

Entrepreneurship with friends/ partners. Publishing magazines monthly and quarterly magazines about food and cookbooks. Worked as designer, art director and photographer.

Designer at "Tuck Video" Cine and Video Production — 2002–2003

Official distributor for Serbia Warner Bros, Sony Pictures and 20th Century Fox, etc. Worked on film promotion campaigns and promotion materials.

Don't hesitate to say hello and inform me about your ideas for collaborations.

Predrag is a Norwegian citizen, living in Bergen, was born in Serbia 1978



Portfolio

pktch.github.io/design

EDUCATION

School of commerce "Jezdimir Lovic" Belgrade (IV degree); MCP – Microsoft Certificated Professional – Network Infrastructure Administrator; Certificated Professional Sommelier; W3School certificate CSS

SKILLS

User Interface and Experience Design

In close collaboration with clients, helping them to improve relation with customer base. Fresh eyes, open and creative approach help designing inclusive and accessible product or service experience that fits seamlessly into people's lives.

FrontEnd Development

In phase of project development, Predrag can help team with FrontEnd Development. Advanced HTML/CSS skills, working in popular frameworks and minimal JS.

PROJECT REFERENCES

Bundesliga – User Interface & Experience research for mobile device fort the live broadcast, conference- simultaneous game play watching (Sixty, 2018); **PremierLeague** – User Interface & Experience study for mobile experience of a live broadcast (Sixty 2019);

Allsvenskan – Competition, 1st prize for design. Broadcast graphics for TV and mobile experience design. (Sixty 2020);

Tencent – Interactive broadcast experience design and graphics for mobile (Sixty 2020);

VICE – Case study- how to incorporate eShop widget on mobile while watching program (Sixty 2019);

CBS – Interactive infographics, Q&A interface, mobile TV experience design (Sixty 2019);

BonaMea – User Interface & Experience, Branding, website. (Intutor, 2016); MyKid – User Interface & Experience, Branding, website. (Intutor, 2014)... TSP, Trafikkskole portalen (today's TABS) Product design for administration, booking system that became choice of over 80% traffic schools in Norway.

CONTACT REFERENCES

Asle Birkeland fmr Design VP, co-founder Sixty, tel: +47 952 15;

Bjarte Århus CEO Intutor AS, tel: +47 901 81 141;